{
    "subject": "Stefania_Grodzie\u0144ska",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Jerzy_Jurandot",
    "human_readable": "Stefania Grodzie\u0144ska is married to Jerzy Jurandot.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9883260130882263,
            "question": "Is there a known marriage between Jerzy Jurandot and Stefania Grodzie\u0144ska?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9560285806655884,
            "question": "To whom is Stefania Grodzie\u0144ska married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9551176428794861,
            "question": "Is Stefania Grodzie\u0144ska married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.930112898349762,
            "question": "Name the person married to Jerzy Jurandot."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9282706379890442,
            "question": "What can you tell about the relationship between Stefania Grodzie\u0144ska and Jerzy Jurandot?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9021556973457336,
            "question": "Who is married to Jerzy Jurandot?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8756994605064392,
            "question": "What relationship do Jerzy Jurandot and Stefania Grodzie\u0144ska share?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8266831636428833,
            "question": "Who is Stefania Grodzie\u0144ska?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7583518624305725,
            "question": "What is the name of Jerzy Jurandot's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39636796712875366,
            "question": "Is Jerzy Jurandot single?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Stefania Grodzie\u0144ska is married to Jerzy Jurandot.",
            "html": "yago_19019_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Jerzy Jurandot's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_19019_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Stefania Grodzie\u0144ska?",
            "html": "yago_19019_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What relationship do Jerzy Jurandot and Stefania Grodzie\u0144ska share?",
            "html": "yago_19019_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19019_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19019_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19019_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19019_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19019_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19019_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19019_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19019_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19019_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19019_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format containing the answer:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all four documents provided in the context information mention that Jerzy Jurandot was married to Stefania Grodzienska."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents state that \"Stefania Grodzienska was previously married to Jerzy Jurandot\" and \"She was married to Jerzy Jurandot,\" which supports the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}